Even though we're not going to use anything to
虽然我们不会在手机上
do with the camera or the images on our phone,
使用任何相机或图片功能
I think it would be fun to play around with using the images,
但是了解下图片使用功能会比较有趣
specifically with Riak Native and with Expo we can see how easy it is.
尤其是对于 React Native 和 Expo 可以知道使用图片功能多么的简单
So what we're going to do in this video is we will pick
在本视频中
an image from our camera roll on the phone,
我们将从手机上的相册中选择一张图片
and then we will edit that image and then we will just show it to the view.
然后编辑该图片 并显示在视图中
So we are going to need to import a few different things.
我们需要导入一些内容
One of those is image editor from Riak native,
首先从 react-native 中导入 ImageEditor
let's also get touchable opacity in here as well.
此外 导入 TouchableOpacity
And then obviously image.
明显还需要导入 Image
So, that looks good,
看起来不错
and then what we need to do is let's
然后从 Expo 中
import image picker which is going to be coming from Expo.
导入 ImagePicker
So the first thing I'm going to do is add a state property of the image to our component,
首先向组件添加一个 image 状态属性
and then let's add a pick image method.
然后添加 pickImage 方法
And what we are going to say here is we are going to say when ever this function runs,
每当该函数运行时
go ahead and call image picker dot launch image library async,
则调用 ImagePicker.launchImageLibraryAsync
and then we are going to pass in a few different
传入几个不同的设置
settings.We will say allow editing to be true,
将 allowEditing 设为 true
so I'll be able to edit it, and then we want the aspect ratio to be 2:1,
从而能够编辑图片 然后将 aspect 设为 2:1
and then when this resolves,
完毕后
we will have a result here,
这里将出现一个结果
and now we can say if result dot canceled is a thing,
如果 result.cancelled 成立
just go ahead and return,
则 return
and if not then what we want to do is we want to
如果不成立
call our image editor component dot crop image.
则调用 ImageEditor.cropImage
We will pass in the URI property on
传入调用 launchImageLibraryAsync 时
the result object that we got back when we called launch image library async.
获得的 result 对象的 URI 属性
And then the second argument we're going to pass to crop image is just some settings.
向 cropImage 传入的第二个参数是一些设置
We will say offset X zero Y zero.
输入 offset:
Let's go ahead and add some size to it.
添加 size
Say width is going to be the result dot width.
width 将为 result.width
And then the height is going to be result dot height.
height 将为 result.height
Next, display size, let's give it a width of 200 and a height of 100.
接着 对于 displaySize 将 width 设为 200 height 设为 100
And then last we want the resize mode to be contained, all right.
最后 将 resizeMode 设为 contain
So, this is the second argument we're passing to crop image.
这些就是传入 cropImage 的第二个参数
The third argument is going to be a function that's going to receive the modified URI.
第三个参数是一个函数 它将接收修改后的 URI
So when we get that, we will just call set state.
获得该 URI 后 调用 setState
And what we're going to pass it is we're going to say we want image to be this new URI.
然后在此处 我们希望此 image 为这个新的 URI
And then finally as the last argument to this invocation right here,
这个函数调用的最后一个参数
we will pass another function,
是另一个函数
and if there is an error we'll just log error for now, that looks good.
如果出现错误 则暂时记录错误 看起来不错
All right, so pick image looks pretty good right now I don't see any errors,
pickImage 设置好了 没有看到任何错误
doesn't seem like we're getting any errors in our application yet either.
应用暂时没有出现任何错误
All right let's go ahead and head down to render.
向下转到 render
In render what we want to do is let's say we
在 render 中
have this touchable component and when it's pressed,
添加这个可触摸组件
what we are going to do is we will run the stop pick image,
当它被点击后 我们将运行 this.pickImage
the text inside of here let's just say open camera roll,
在 Text 组件中 显示文本“Open Camera Roll”
and now the last thing we want to do is we will come down here and we will say if,
最后 我们将在这里输入...
let's go ahead and grab image first which is coming from the states,
先在这里从 this.state 中获取 image
and we will say if image is a thing then what we
如果 image 成立
want to do is let's go ahead and render the image.
则渲染该图片
It will give it a style of styles dot image which I created down here,
将 style 设为 styles.img 我在下面创建了 img 样式
and then we are going to give it a source and the URI is going to be image.
提供一个 source URI 将为 image
All right so now what we expect to have happen is
现在会发生的情况是
we open the camera roll when we press on this button,
点击此按钮后打开相册
that goes and runs pick image so we do open the camera roll, we pick our image,
然后运行 pickImage 因此打开相册并选择图片
and then once we have that we go ahead and crop it with
获得图片之后 按照这些设置对图片进行剪裁
these settings so the width will be 200, the height will be 100,
width 将为 200 height 将为 100
and then if that cropping is successful,
如果剪裁成功
we will add the image to
我们将该图片添加到本地状态上
our local state and then we will then show that image to the view.
然后将该图片显示到视图上
So let's go and see if this works.
看看是否可行
So first we open the camera roll and select an image,
先打开相册 选择图片
then we crop it and show it to the view. So there we go.
然后剪裁并显示到视图上 成功了